Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sachin-khairnar-4873b199 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Electronics
Problem Solving
Calibration

sachin khairnar

Electrical Engineer at Qualitrol

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Experienced Electrical Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the electrical and electronic manufacturing industry. Skilled in Field Support, Field Operations, Field Service, Electrical Engineering, and Project Planning. Strong engineering professional graduated from R.H. Sapat, Gokhale College Of Engineering.

Experience

Qualitrol
Electrical Engineer
June 2016 - Present (7 years 3 months)
Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Fortive Electrical Engineer June 2016 - Present (7 years 3 months) Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Education

R.H. Sapat, Gokhale College Of Engineering

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical Engineering · (2010 - 2014)

MET's Bhujbal knowledge city, Nashik Diploma, Electrical Engineering (2008 - 2010)